Dr. Jaehong Yoon

CONTACT Information UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA, CHAPEL HILL, NC

E-MAIL: jhyoon@cs.unc.edu

LINKS: HOMEPAGE, GOOGLE SCHOLAR, TWITTER

RESEARCH INTERESTS I've been focusing on tackling practical and real-world challenges to understand humans and impact our real lives through ever-evolving embodied AI systems with multiple agents & modalities. My research interest includes the following topics:

- Multimodal/Video Large Language Models: Comprehension, Generation, and Faithfulness
- Compositional Generalization: Continual Learning and Compositional Reasoning
- Efficient Training/Inference: Parameter-efficient Learning, Model Compression, and Federated Learning

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Postdoctoral Research Associat Advisor: Prof. Mohit Bansa	, ,	08/2023 - Current
Postdoctoral Research Associat Advisor: Prof. Sung Ju Hw	, ,	03/2023 - 08/2023
Visiting Student, Weizmann Institute of Science, Israel Host: Prof. Yonina Eldar		10/2022 - 11/2022
Research Intern, Microsoft Research, China Visual Computing Group Mentor: Dr. Yue Cao		11/2021 - 04/2022

Research Scientist, MLAI Lab., KAIST, South Korea

02/2018 - 08/2018

EDUCATION

KAIST, Daejeon, South Korea

Ph.D., School of Computing,

Aug 2018 - Feb 2023

- Thesis: "On-device, Online Continual Learning for the Real World"
- The Best Ph.D. Dissertation Award from KAIST College of Engineering
- The Best Ph.D. Dissertation Award from KAIST School of Computing
- Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence (MLAI) Lab
- Adviser: Prof. Sung Ju Hwang
- Area of Study: Machine Learning

UNIST, Ulsan, South Korea

M.S., Computer Science,

Aug 2016 - Feb 2018

- Thesis: "Combined Group and Exclusive Sparsity for Deep Neural Networks"
- Adviser: Prof. Sung Ju Hwang
- Area of Study: Machine Learning

B.S., Computer Science Engineering,

Mar 2012 - Aug 2016

• Biological Science Minor

Conference Publications

*: equal contribution

[C22] Mementos: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Multimodal Large Language Model Reasoning over Image Sequences

Xiyao Wang, Yuhang Zhou, Xiaoyu Liu, Hongjin Lu, Yuancheng Xu, Feihong He, **Jaehong Yoon**, Taixi Lu, Gedas Bertasius, Mohit Bansal, Huaxiu Yao, and Furong Huang Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics (ACL) 2024, Bangkok, Thailand

[C21] STELLA: Continual Audio-Video Pre-training with Spatio-Temporal Localized Alignment

Jaewoo Lee*, Jaehong Yoon*, Wonjae Kim, Yunji Kim, and Sung Ju Hwang CVPR 2024 Workshop on Continual Learning (CLVision)
International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2024, Vienna, Austria

[C20] EVEREST: Efficient Masked Video Autoencoder by Removing Redundant Spatiotemporal Tokens

Sunil Hwang*, Jaehong Yoon*, Youngwan Lee*, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2024, Vienna, Austria

[C19] BECoTTA: Input-dependent Online Blending of Experts for Continual Test-time Adaptation

Daeun Lee*, Jaehong Yoon*, and Sung Ju Hwang CVPR 2024 Workshop on Test-Time Adaptation International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2024, Vienna, Austria

[C18] Carpe Diem: On the Evaluation of World Knowledge in Lifelong Language Models

Yujin Lee, Jaehong Yoon, Seonghyeon Ye, Sangmin Bae, Namgyu Ho, Sung Ju Hwang, and Se Young Yun
NeurIPS 2023 Workshop on Synthetic Data Generation with Generative AI, Oral

NeurIPS 2023 Workshop on Synthetic Data Generation with Generative AI, Oral
The North American Chapter of the Association for Computational Linguistics (NAACL)
2024, Mexico City, Mexico

[C17] Multimodal Representation Learning by Alternating Unimodal Adaptation XiaoHui Zhang, Jaehong Yoon, Mohit Bansal, and Huaxiu Yao The IEEE/CVF Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition Conference (CVPR) 2024, Seattle, Washington

[C16] ECoFLaP: Efficient Coarse-to-Fine Layer-Wise Pruning for Vision-Language Models

Yi-lin Sung, Jaehong Yoon, and Mohit Bansal International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2024, Vienna, Austria

[C15] Analyzing and Mitigating Object Hallucination in Large Vision-Language Models Yiyang Zhou*, Chenhang Cui*, Jaehong Yoon, Linjun Zhang, Chelsea Finn, Mohit Bansal, and Huaxiu Yao

NeurIPS 2023 Workshop on Instruction Tuning and Instruction Following International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2024, Vienna, Austria

[C14] Progressive Fourier Neural Representation for Sequential Video Compilation Haeyong Kang, Jaehong Yoon, Dahyun Kim, Sung Ju Hwang, and Chang D. Yoo International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2024, Vienna, Austria

[C13] Text-Guided Token Selection for Text-to-Image Synthesis with Token-based Diffusion Models

Jaewoong Lee*, Sangwon Jang*, Jaehyeong Jo, **Jaehong Yoon**, Yunji Kim, Jin-Hwa Kim, Jung-Woo Ha, Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV) 2023, Paris, France

[C12] Continual Learners are Incremental Model Generalizers Jaehong Yoon, Sung Ju Hwang, Yue Cao International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2023, Hawaii, USA

[C11] Personalized Subgraph Federated Learning

Jinheon Baek*, Wonyong Jeong*, Jiongdao Jin, **Jaehong Yoon**, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2023, Hawaii, USA

[C10] On the Soft-Subnetwork for Few-shot Class Incremental Learning Haeyong Kang, Jaehong Yoon, Sultan Madjid, Sung Ju Hwang, Chang D. Yoo International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2023, Kigali, Rwanda

[C9] Bitwidth Heterogeneous Federated Learning with Progressive Weight Dequantization

Jaehong Yoon*, Geon Park*, Wonyong Jeong, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2022, Baltimore, USA

[C8] Forget-free Continual Learning with Winning Subnetworks Haeyong Kang*, Rusty Mina*, Sultan Madjid, Jaehong Yoon, Mark Hasegawa-Johnson, Sung Ju Hwang, and Chang D. Yoo International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2022, Baltimore, USA

[C7] Rethinking the Representational Continuity: Towards Unsupervised Continual Learning

Divyam Madaan, Jaehong Yoon, Yuanchun Li, Yunxin Liu, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2022, Virtual Oral Presentation (Acceptance Rate = 54/3391 = 1.6%)

- [C6] Online Coreset Selection for Rehearsal-based Continual Learning Jaehong Yoon, Divyam Madaan, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2022, Virtual
- [C5] Federated Continual Learning with Weighted Inter-client Transfer Jaehong Yoon*, Wonyong Jeong*, Giwoong Lee, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang ICML 2020 Workshop on Lifelong Machine Learning Workshop International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2021, Virtual

[C4] Federated Semi-supervised Learning with Inter-Client Consistency & Disjoint Learning

Wonyong Jeong, Jaehong Yoon, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang ICML 2020 Workshop on Federated Learning for User Privacy and Data Confidentiality Workshop, Long Presentation, Best Student Paper Award International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2021, Virtual

[C3] Scalable and Order-robust Continual Learning with Additive Parameter Decomposition

Jaehong Yoon, Saehoon Kim, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2020, Addis ababa, Ethiopia, Virtual

- [C2] Lifelong Learning with Dynamically Expandable Networks Jaehong Yoon, Eunho Yang, Jeongtae Lee, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2018, Vancouver, Canada
- [C1] Combined Group and Exclusive Sparsity for Deep Neural Networks Jaehong Yoon and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2017, Sydney, Australia

Preprints

[P5] EnvGen: Bootstrapping Embodied Agent Training with LLM-Generated Environments

Abhay Zala, Jaemin Cho, Han Lin, **Jaehong Yoon**, and Mohit Bansal arXiv:2403.12014, 2024.

[P4] SELMA: Learning and Merging Skill-Specific Text-to-Image Experts with Auto-Generated Data

Jialu Li, Jaemin Cho, Yi-lin Sung, **Jaehong Yoon**, and Mohit Bansal arXiv:2403.06952, 2024.

[P3] CREMA: Multimodal Compositional Video Reasoning via Efficient Modular Adaptation and Fusion

Shoubin Yu*, **Jaehong Yoon***, and Mohit Bansal arXiv:2402.05889, 2024.

[P2] Rapid Structural Pruning of Neural Networks with Set-based Task-Adaptive Meta-Pruning

Minyoung Song, Jaehong Yoon, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang arXiv:2006.12139, 2020.

[P1] Adaptive Network Sparsification with Dependent Beta-Bernoulli Dropout Juho Lee, Saehoon Kim, Jaehong Yoon, Haebeom Lee, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang arXiv:1805.10896, 2018.

Workshop Presentations

[W1] BiTAT: Neural Network Binarization with Task-dependent Aggregated Transformation

Geon Park*, **Jaehong Yoon***, Haiyang Zhang, Xing Zhang, Sung Ju Hwang, and Yonina C. Eldar

ECCV 2022 Workshop on Computational Aspects of Deep Learning (CADL)

PATENTS (US ONLY)

Method and Apparatus with Neural Network and Training

Jaehong Yoon, Saehoon Kim, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang US 20210256374 A1, Aug 2021

Electronic Apparatus and Method for Re-learning Trained Model Jaehong Yoon, Eunho Yang, Jeongtae Lee, and Sung Ju Hwang US 20180357539 A1, Dec 2018

REVIEWER SERVICES

International Conferences

2022 - 2024 Conference on Lifelong Learning Agents (CoLLAs)

2019 - 2024 International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML)

2019 - 2024 International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR)

2018 - 2023 Neural Information Processing System (NeurIPS)

2020 International Joint Conferences on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI)

2020 Association for the Advancement of Artificial Intelligence (AAAI)

INTERNATIONAL JOURNALS

2022 Journal of Artificial Intelligence Research (JAIR)

2020, 2022 IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems (TNNLS)

2021, 2023 IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (TPAMI)

2021~IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking (ToN)

2020 Neural Networks

AWARDS

The Best Ph.D. Dissertation Award from KAIST College of Engineering, 2023

NeurIPS Top Reviewers Award, 2019

NAVER Ph.D. Fellowship Award, 2017

INVITED TALKS

Lightweight Video & Multimodal Learning

LG AI, 2023

Towards Continuously Evolving AI

Edinburgh University, 2023

Federated and Continual Learning with Heterogeneous Clients

Prof. Eric Xing's Group, CMU & MBZUAI, 2023

Online Coreset Selection for Rehearsal-based Conitnual Learning

Prof. Kristin Grauman's Group, UT Austin, 2022

Representational Continuity for Unsupervised Continual Learning

Korea Computer Congress (KCC), 2022

Lifelong Learning with Dynamically Expandable Networks

Samsung SDS, 2019

Tech. Talk from NAVER Corp., 2018

Tech. Open Connect (T-T.O.C) from SK-Telecom, 2018

Combined Group and Exclusive Sparsity for Deep Neural Networks

Korea Software Congress (KSC), 2017

References

Prof. Mohit Bansal, Professor, University of North Carolina (UNC) Chapel Hill, US

Email: mbansal@cs.unc.edu

Prof. Sung Ju Hwang, Associate Professor, KAIST, South Korea

Email: sjhwang82@kaist.ac.kr

Prof. Eunho Yang, Associate Professor, KAIST, South Korea

Email: eunhoy@kaist.ac.kr

Dr. Yue Cao, Senior Researcher, Mircosoft Research Asia, China

Email: caoyue10@gmail.com

Prof. Yonina Eldar, Professor, Weizmann Institute of Science, Israel

Email: yonina.eldar@weizmann.ac.il